crazycameras.co.uk 2009-06-18

# Crazy Cameras - Privacy Policy

|   
---  
|  |  |  |  |  |  | » Privacy Policy »  
---|---  
  |   

This privacy statement sets out how [www.crazycameras.co.uk](http://www.crazycameras.co.uk/) uses the information its users provide when using the website. Crazycameras.co.uk is committed to ensuring that our user’s information is protected. You can be assured that the information you provide us will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact crazycameras.co.uk by email at [support@crazycameras.co.uk](mailto:support@crazycameras.co.uk)

  1. **Information Collection and Use**
    1. **Information Collection**

Crazycameras.co.uk is the sole owner of the information collected its website. Crazycameras.co.uk collects information from our users at several different points on our Web site. A user must provide contact information (such as name, email, and delivery address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiry date). This information is used for billing purposes and for order fulfillment. We do not provide credit card information, your user ID or any password to anyone outside of Crazycameras.co.uk. 

    2. **Information Use**

We will use the following personal information in order to process your order from our site: Full Name, Address, Telephone numbers, e-mail address, and any other information deemed necessary.

    3. **Membership Program**

Membership is not essential to make a purchase. Customers who choose to join our membership program are subject to the same Privacy Policy as non-members. We may ask for additional information from users who sign up for membership. 

When you become a Member of Crazycameras.co.uk or our other Websites, we ask you for personal information such as your name, email address, your firms address, a user ID and an account password. We may provide Member Information to companies or individuals who may wish to contact you to offer their goods or services.

We send update emails to our Members from time to time, to keep them up to date with product launches, promotions, and site news. Members can opt-out of these emails at the time of registration, or by replying to the original email with the word "unsubscribe" in the subject line, or by emailing [support@crazycameras.co.uk](mailto:support@crazycameras.co.uk)

    4. **Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's computer tied to information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. When you visit our website, we send one or more cookies to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. More information on cookies can be found here: [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).

    5. **Server Logs**

When you visit our websites, our server automatically records information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These Server Logs may include information such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your visit and the identity of any cookies that were sent to your browser. 

    6. **User Communications**

When you provide feedback or send inquiries to Crazycameras.co.uk, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

    7. **Affiliated Sites**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. You should note that we do not have any control over that other website once you leave our website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read the privacy policies of those Company’s. 

  2. **Communications from the Site**

Crazycameras.co.uk only processes personal information for the purposes described in this privacy policy. In addition to the above, such purposes include: 

    1. **Special Offers and Updates**

We send all new members a welcoming email to verify password and username. Our members will, from time to time, receive information on products, services, special deals, and a newsletter.

    2. **Customer Service**

We communicate with users on a regular basis to provide requested services and in regards to issues relating to their account. We reply via email or phone, in accordance with the users wishes. 

    3. **Legal Disclaimer**

Though crazycameras.co.uk makes every effort to preserve user privacy, we may need to disclose personal information when required by the court of law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding or a court order. 

    4. **Choice/Opt-out**

Our users are given the opportunity to 'opt-out' of having their information used for purposes not directly related to our site at the point where we ask for information. 

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications may opt-out of receiving these communications by selecting the un-subscribe link included in each email or by sending an email to [support@crazycameras.co.uk](mailto:support@crazycameras.co.uk)

    5. **Security**

This Web site takes every precaution to protect our users' information. When users submit sensitive information via the Web site, their information is protected both online and off-line.

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access or alteration, disclosure, or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to Personal Information to Crazycameras.co.uk employees, contractors and agents who are required to have knowledge of this information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations

If users have any questions about the security at our Web site, users can send an email to [support@crazycameras.co.uk](mailto:support@crazycameras.co.uk)

    6. **Notification of Changes**

We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. For additional information about the Websites, Crazycameras.co.uk or our Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@crazycameras.co.uk](mailto:support@crazycameras.co.uk)

|    
|  |
